# DANIEL APODACA

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER



#### CONTACT

+52-(636)-106-63-34 apodacaduron@gmail.com https://dapodaca.com

#### **EDUCATION**

# INSTITUTO TECNOLÓGICO **SUPERIOR DE NUEVO CASAS GRANDES**

2014 - 2018 Computer Systems Engineer

- -Moved to a new city for my professional practices.
- -Developed a Laravel based system for a company.
- -Imparted a course of design using photoshop.
- -Collaborated on the organization of many school events.
- -Completed an entrepreneurship course.
- -Approved EGEL exam.

## **SKILLS**

FRAMEWORKS DATABASES Vue.is SOL Angular 6+ MySQL React MongoDB Ionic

**OTHER TOOLS** Flutter VS Code Electron Git Express.is

Linux OS Laravel Photoshop Lightroom

**HOSTING** CPanel Subdomains DNS

Audition Premiere After Effects

SEO

Optimization

#### **PROFILE**

I am a Computer Systems Engineer with 3+ years of experience in web development and design, who has developed personal products and for enterprise clients from Mexico and United States. I usually work with custom projects specific to the business needs of a client, anything from Web Applications (Frontend / Backend), Mobile Apps, Database / Server Management, Web Deployment, Graphic Design and Video Production.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

CONTROLLA · FULL TIME / DEC 2018 - PRESENT

Designed and coded landing pages, worked on specific custom CRM and ERP systems, mobile apps on flutter, REST API usage, synchronized a COMPAQ local database through an electron client to store in the cloud, created an interactive map for house selling, web deployment, database managment.

## WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

EPSILON SOFT S DE RLMI XNET · FULL TIME / JUL 2018 - DEC 2018 Developed several Landing Pages, contributed on PHP Invoice Systems, added new features to a restaurant order taking system from a big restaurant franchise, created and managed websites through ssh on a Linux server and collaborated with the installation of Access Points on a building in Acapulco, Guerrero.

#### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

INSTITUTO TECNOLÓGICO SUPERIOR DE NUEVO CASAS GRANDES · PART TIME SEP 2016 - MAY 2018

Worked as a photographer, video editor, motion graphics artist and managing social media.

#### **PHOTOGRAPHER**

MAR 2017 - MAR 2018

I have contributed on Unsplash with more than 80 professional photographies and generated over 44 million views and 350 thousand downloads, placing me under the 1000th most downloaded contributors ever, the pictures have been featured on big platforms like Trello, Adobe Spark, BuzzFeed, PicsArt, Unfold, Invision, Over and more independent businesses.